hey everyone I want to uh invite you to
check out this message entitled The
Ghost Writer um it will absolutely
revolutionize your understanding of
justification by faith the law of God
the works of the flesh uh powerful
message check it out and be
blessed
[Music]
the Ghost
Writer the question is what is a ghost
writer a ghost writer is an individual a
person who writes on behalf of another
but gives them the
credit a ghost writer is hired to write
works that officially credit another
person as the
author usually a ghost writer will not
get any credit or seek to take any
credit to
himself a Ghost
Rider Works to make you look
good a ghost writer works on
autobiographies on speeches songs
screenplays
Memoirs a ghost writer is usually
employed when a writer does not have
enough skill to write effectively on his
own how would
you how would
you like to have your own Ghost
Rider I'm just going to ask put a one in
the chat
if you would like to have your own Ghost
Writer someone who writes
anonymously that credits
you that stays in the background and
wants to make you look good what if yes
beloved what if you could have your
own personal ghost
writer well
today I want to let you know about the
most
powerful Ghost
Rider that there
is and that Ghost Rider beloved is found
in John chapter 14 come with me to the
screen John chapter
14 and verse 16 Jesus says I will pray
the father
and he shall give you another
comforter that you may abide that he may
abide with you
forever Jesus as he is preparing to
leave the Earth says I'm going to send
the comforter which is the holy spirit
which is the Holy Ghost to be with you
now please note with me in John chapter
16 and verse 13 Jesus continues on and
he says here how be it when he the
spirit of Truth is come he will guide
you into all Truth for he shall not
speak of himself he shall not speak of
himself he shall not take credit to
himself but whatsoever he shall hear
that shall he
speak and he will show you things to
come verse 16 or verse 14
for he will glorify he shall glorify me
for he shall receive of mine and shall
show it unto you now let's pause here
for a
second Jesus says of this Holy Ghost
this holy spirit that that when the Holy
Spirit
comes he is going to
glorify
Jesus so the question is what does it
mean to glorify Jesus he's not going to
speak of himself he is going to glorify
Jesus he's going to stay in the
background and
glorify Jesus well what does it mean to
glorify look with me on the screen for a
moment to
glorify is the same thing as to
magnify that's what it means to glorify
something to magnify and to magnify it
means to make something appear
larger especially as with a lens or a
microscope so then what we can gather
from this is that the work of the holy
spirit is to
glorify
Jesus it is to
glorify our Lord to show us something
about our Lord to show us something to
magnify as has with a lens something
regarding our
Lord so the question becomes what is the
Holy
Ghost seeking to show
us how is he seeking to
glorify the lord well we can find the
answer as we go back into the Old
Testament there is an encounter that
Moses has with God it is a discussion in
which Moses is going to ask a question
that beloved really every last one of us
should be asking here is the
question in Exodus 33 and verse 17 the
Bible says and the Lord said unto Moses
I will do this thing
also that I have spoken that thou has
spoken for thou Hast found Grace in my
sight and I Know Thee by name
and he said beseech
thee show me thy
Glory Moses wanted to see the glory of
God all of us should desire to see the
glory of God the work of the holy spirit
is to show us the glory of God now put a
one in the chat if you are foll
following me so far the work of the
spirit The Ghost
Writer the Holy Ghost is to show us the
glory of Jesus to magnify or
glorify Jesus we see Moses saying Lord
show me thy glory and I want you to
understand I want you to see how the
Lord defines his own Glory so let's go
back to the
screen and notice with me verse 19 in
answer to the question that Moses asks
show me thy Glory the Lord says I will
make all my goodness pass before thee
and I will proclaim the name of the Lord
before thee and will be gracious to whom
I will be gracious and I will show Mercy
unto whom I will show mercy and he said
thou c not see my face for there shall
no man see me and live so please note
please note that that when God when
Moses asks show me thy
Glory the response is I will make all my
goodness pass before you so what is the
glory of God beloved according to what
we've just read the glory of God is his
goodness the glory of Christ is his
goodness
again put a one in the chat if you're
following along so far we're building a
case to reveal the importance and the
work of the Ghost Rider notice with me
again notice with me again in Exodus 33:
211 continuing on and the Lord said
behold there is a place by me and thou
shalt stand upon a rock and it shall
come to pass while my Glory passeth by
that I will will put thee in a cliff of
The Rock and will cover thee my hand
will I pass and will cover thee with my
hand will I pass by and I will take away
mine hand and thou shalt see my back
Parts but my face shall not be seen the
glory of
God is the goodness of God and Moses is
is
shown the GL the glory the goodness of
God in John 12: 23 what we need to
understand what this goodness is what is
this Glory of Jesus that equates to his
goodness notice with me John 12:23 here
the Bible
says Jesus speaking listen to me now
Jesus speaking answered them and said
the hour is come that the son of man
should be what put that word in the chat
for me please the son of man should be
glorified verily verily I say unto you
except the corn of wheat fall into the
ground and die it abideth alone but if
it die it bringeth forth much and what's
that next word put it in the chat for me
it bringeth forth much fruit so please
note Jesus in speaking of his own
glorification is pointing to the work
he's about to do on the cross his death
burial and Resurrection his
crucifixion is the
glory it is the
goodness in John
13:31 again after Judas goes out to
betray him the Bible says therefore when
he was gone out Jesus said now is the
son of man
glorified and God is glorified in him if
God be glorified in him God shall also
glorify him in himself and shall
straightway glorify him Jesus once again
is showing here that his
glory is his death on the cross for
Humanity that death on the cross we are
told Veronica produces
fruit please follow along this is why
Paul writes in Galatians chapter 6 and
verse4 God
forbid that I should what
Glory save in the cross of our Lord
Jesus Christ by whom the world is
crucified unto me and I unto the
world Paul here is telling
us that the only Glory worth anything is
the glory of the cross the place where
Christ died for us why because as we
look at the cross beloved we are looking
at the glory of God the work of the
spirit the work of the ghost riter
follow me here the work of the ghost
riter is to magnify to us the glory of
God the glory of Christ which means the
work of the holy spirit is to show us
Christ on the cross which is the
goodness of
God how do we know this is the goodness
of God well the Bible tells us in Romans
chapter
1:16 I am not a ashamed of the Gospel
stop for a moment right there what does
the word gospel
mean what is the
gospel what does gospel
mean come on when we say the gospel
another another way we say the gospel
when we say hey we're preaching the
gospel we're saying we're preaching the
what yes Clint yes Christie yes Jodie it
is the good
let me just pause for a second right
there y' it is the good news or if we
can flip that the news of the goodness
of
God are y'all with me the
cross is the good news or the news of
the goodness of God this is why I come
with me back to Romans chapter 1:16 it
says for I not ashamed of the gospel of
Christ for it is the power of God unto
salvation to everyone that believeth it
is the power of God unto salvation to
everyone that believeth to the Jew first
and also to the Greek for therein is
watch
this therein is the righteousness of God
revealed from Faith to Faith as it is
written the just shall live by faith in
other words
something about looking at the cross is
designed to bring to mind the truth of
the righteousness of God which is that
the just shall live by
faith put a one in the chat y' if you
follow me so
far the the work of the Ghost Rider the
work of the holy spirit is to show us
the glory of God which is the goodness
of God which is Christ CH on the
cross now why is the holy spirit why is
the Ghost Rider seeking to show us this
well let's check it out come with me to
2 Corinthians Chapter 3 Verse
18 the Bible here says but we all with
open face
beholding as in a glass the what come on
y'all come on you guys what are we
beholding we are with open face
beholding as in a
glass the glory of the Lord are changed
into the same image from glory to glory
even as by the spirit of the Lord so
let's break this
down the reason the holy spirit is
trying trying to focus our attention on
the glory of the Lord is so that that
same Spirit can begin to change us into
the image of the Lord are y'all with me
so
far are you'all following the the the
thought process
here by
beholding the cross which is the
goodness of God which is the glory of
God God the spirit the Ghost Rider can
now go to work in us remember the work
of a Ghost Rider is to make you look
good the work of a Ghost Rider is the
Ghost Rider stays in the background and
begins to write on your behalf it
credits to you something that is not
your own put a seven in the chat if
y'all are following if y'all are like
okay pastor we get this now we
understand we understand why the holy
spirit is seeking to fix our attention
on the cross because once our eyes and
our minds lock onto the work of the
cross the Ghost Rider can now begin to
write the Ghost Rider can now begin to
change so what is the work what is he
writing what is he trying to do let's go
to the Book of Ezekiel chapter 36 and we
will see exactly what the Ghost Rider
why the Ghost Rider is trying to to to
keep us focused on the cross watch this
in Ezekiel 36: 26 the Bible says here a
new heart also will I give you and a new
spirit will I put within you and I will
take away the Stony flesh out of your
heart and I will give you a heart of
Flesh and I will put my spirit within
you and cause
you cause
you cause you to walk in my statutes and
you shall keep my judgments and do them
so check this out you
all God is telling us that the work of
the Ghost Rider Sharon yes is to re
write the book of the
heart yes yes yes the work of The Ghost
Writer is to write God's law and
character upon our heart he looks at our
work Ghost Writer I I need a Ghost Rider
why well you know I was trying to write
and I don't think I'm doing such a good
job you know I got a whole bunch of
mistakes and you know sometimes I just
don't know how to put these things
together so the Ghost Rider looks at
your work and he's like okay well if you
want me to to work if you want me to to
get involved in this what I'm going to
need you to
do what I'm going to need you to do is
I'm going to need you to just focus on
the glory of God now I don't want you to
write you put the pen
[Music]
down you put the pen down let me handle
the pen all I want you to do all I want
you to do is just
stay focused on the glory yes Annette
hand the pen
over hand the pen over I will do the
writing I will be your ghost come on
y'all I will be your Ghost Rider and
here's what I'm going to do according to
Hebrews chap 8:10 the Bible tells us for
this is the Covenant that I will make
with the house of Israel after those
days say the Lord I I will put my law
into their minds and write them in their
hearts and I will be to them a God and
they shall be to me my people a people
now if we go back to Ezekiel 36 we you I
want you to pay attention to something
very carefully because the text said I
will cause you watch this now y'all not
you will cause you to walk walk in my
statutes I will cause you it's as if God
is saying somehow you're walking in my
statutes will be a reflex it's not going
to be something that you
cause it's going to be something that I
cause and and and the cause is the
spirit when the spirit takes the pen it
is a spirit that now causes you it is
the work of the spirit not of you you
cannot cause yourself you cannot force
yourself now some people do Force
themselves but that's not what counts as
justification by faith that's not what
counts as the work of the spirit that's
your
writing not the writing of the Holy
Spirit right so so so now we can begin
to see a very important formula
unfolding come let me show you the
formula in John 1: 29 John the Baptist
listen what the Bible says the next day
John seeth Jesus coming unto him and
saith now here goes the formula y'all
Behold the Lamb of God which taketh away
the sin of the world that's verse 29
John is telling the world Behold the
Lamb of God which takes away the sin of
the world now some something happens
when we Behold the Lamb of God which
takes away the sin of the world what
happens what H watch this y'all in verse
32 John bear record saying I saw the
Spirit descending from heaven like a
dove and it Abode upon him listen to me
listen the holy spirit in the form of a
dove draws the attention mention to
Jesus's
baptism why is the spirit doing this
well according to the Book of Romans
chapter 6 verse3 The Bible says know you
not that so many of us as were baptized
into Jesus Christ were baptized into his
death therefore we are buried with him
by baptism into death that like as
Christ was raised from the dead by the
glory of the father even so we also
should walk in newness of life in other
words beloved
the Holy Spirit descended as Jesus was
going through this ritual which was to
point to his own death burial and
Resurrection in other words the holy
spirit is now highlighting look Behold
the Lamb of God who in this act of
baptism is foreshadowing his own death
in other words beloved what I'm saying
to you is that the holy spirit is
continually
highlighting the death burial and
resurrection of Christ and and and what
I want you to see beloved is that when
once this this this act of Christ
baptism takes place notice what happens
next in Luke 4:1 and Jesus being full of
the Holy Ghost returned from the Jordan
and was led by the spirit into the
Wilderness it's as if it's as if the
holy spirit is saying to us when you
focus your mind on the death burial and
resurrection of Christ I will begin to
come into your life and Lead You just as
I led
Jesus whoa wait a minute so if I want
the spirit to come into my life and
begin writing my future future how many
of you would like your future written
out by the
way you know ghost writers they write
speeches they write Memoirs they write
all kinds of things how many of you
would like to have your future written
out H man if I want my future written
out the holy spirit is saying to me I
need you to focus on the lamb when you
focus on the death bar and resurrection
of Christ I will descend and begin to
lead you just like I led Jesus the Bible
says in Romans 8:14 therefore for as
many as are led by the spirit of God
they are the sons of God this is my
beloved Son in whom I'm well pleased
beloved listen to me the more we focus
on the cross that is where the spirit
meets us and begins to become our ghost
writer put a five in the chat beloved if
you're following if you're catching this
and now I'm going to go back to that
text that we have been focusing on for
the last 6 weeks listen to what the
Bible says in numbers 21:6 the Lord sent
fiery serpents among the people and they
bit the people and much people of Israel
died therefore the people came to Moses
and said we have sinned for we have
spoken against the Lord and against thee
pray unto the Lord that he take away the
serpents from us and Moses prayed for
the people the Bible says and the Lord
said unto Moses make thee a fiery
Serpent and put it on a
pole and it shall come to pass that
everyone that is bitten when he lookth
upon it shall live shall live shall live
and Moses made a serpent of brass and
put it on the pole and it came to pass
that if any man had been bitten when he
beheld The Serpent of brass he lived I
need y'all to understand yes Veronica
that the Holy Spirit doesn't just edit
your paast he rewrites your future
because when you start focusing on
Christ beloved you are basically you are
basically come stepping into a new
future oh man I hope y'all are catching
this listen this is why this is why the
pen of inspiration said powerfully said
this hanging upon the
cross Christ was the
gospel hanging upon the cross Christ was
the Gospel now we have a message Behold
the Lamb of God which taketh away the
sins of the world will not our church
members keep their eyes fixed on a
crucified and Risen Savior in whom their
hopes of eternal life are centered this
is our message our argument our Doctrine
our warning to the impenitent our
encouragement for The Sorrowing the hope
for every believer listen if we can
awaken an interest in men's Minds that
will cause them to fix their eyes on
Christ we may step aside and ask them
only to continue to fix their eyes upon
the Lamb of God thus they receive their
lesson whosoever will come after me let
him deny himself and take up his cross
and follow me he whose Eyes Are Fixed On
Jesus will leave all he will die to
selfishness he will believe in all the
word of God which is so gloriously and
wonderful Yul exalted in Christ beloved
it is the Cross of Christ it is the
Cross of Christ as we behold what he did
for us on the cross the Holy Spirit
comes into us and begins to work a
transformation the spirit Works a
transformation not you not me it is all
we are called to do is behold and give
the pen to The Ghost riter and as we
behold remember back in the old days
when when when and not even in the old
days even now someone is trying to draw
a picture of you you got to strike a
pose and they don't want you to move so
strike the pose and if the artist is
drawing the picture you can't move
listen y'all listen to
me the pose is
this that's it if you could just stay
like
this
and you could do whatever you
want however you want to pose but as
long as your eyes are focused on what he
did at the cross the Holy Spirit the
Ghost Rider begins to do his
work come on y'all I I hope you're
following this this is why first Peter
chap 2: 24 says this who in his own self
bear our sin
on the tree that we being dead to sins
should live unto righteousness by whose
Stripes you are healed when the children
in the Old Testament looked at the
serpent on the pole they were healed by
beholding that wounded
serpent which was a type of Jesus
Christ beloved it is this beholding it
is this
looking that translates the
righteousness of God into us our work
our labor is to
contemplate is to behold is to meditate
is to strike oppose
anet it is to keep our
eyes
focused and meditating on the
mindblowing work of the sacrifice of
Christ so the Bible says Jesus bear our
sins on a tree why is this so important
listen y'all if if this is making sense
to you just just put a seven in the chat
and let me know Pastor we're tracking
with you because I'm about to show you
some things beloved that by the grace of
God is going to revolutionize your walk
listen to
me Jesus buar himself on a tree that
tree is the cross that that is the glory
of God it is the goodness of God and now
and now now check this out y'all in
Matthew 7 verse1 17 listen to what the
Bible
says every good tree bringeth forth good
[Music]
fruit yes yeah every good tree bring
forth good fruit but a corrupt tree
bringeth forth evil fruit a good tree
cannot bring forth evil fruit neither
can a corrupt tree bring forth good
fruit so in other words beloved if I am
beholding the tree of Calvary if I'm
beholding the tree of the Gospel the
good news tree if I'm beholding that
work that Christ did on the cross it is
a good tree and good trees do
what come on put it in the chat y'all
what does a good tree
produce a good tree produces good fruit
the gospel the good news the glory of
God the goodness of God is summarized in
that tree of Calvary in what Christ did
for us so if I am beholding the good
tree what's going to happen is good
fruit is going to come from that because
a good tree cannot produce bad
fruit so oh wait a minute Pastor so hold
on so what you're saying what you're
saying is that by beholding the tree of
Calvary the Holy
Spirit comes in me and starts producing
fruit the
fruit of the spirit
oh yeah yeah yeah come on come on y'all
Galatians chapter 5 Galatians CH 5 note
what it says note what it says the
fruit but the
fruit the fruit of the
spirit is love joy peace longsuffering
gentleness goodness Faith meekness
Temperance against such there is no law
and they that are Christ have crucified
the Flesh and the affections with the
affections thereof so then listen to me
the way we get love joy peace
longsuffering gentleness goodness Faith
meekness Temperance is by Focus focusing
upon the picture of love joy peace
longsuffering gentleness goodness Faith
meekness Temperance and that
picture is the
cross when you are looking at the cross
beloved when you are looking at the work
of Christ on the cross what you are
looking at literally is love love joy
peace longsuffering gentleness goodness
Faith meekness Temperance the P the
spirit is trying to write these things
on our heart and then he gives us the
credit even though it's not our
work come on
y'all that good tree the cross when we
behold it the spirit says okay you're
looking now I'm going to come into your
life because you're looking you I have I
have been given permission to now work
in you because you are looking at the
serpent on the pole you are looking at
the goodness of God you are looking at
the glory of God now stay there strike
the pose and stay there but do you need
me to no no no no no I just need you to
strike the
pose I just need you to
look
whatever you whatever pose but make sure
your eyes are stayed on the cross make
sure your eyes are stayed on the Lamb of
God which taketh away the sins of the
world and so as we're looking as we're
watching as we're looking and
contemplating we begin to see on that
cross love joy peace longsuffering gentl
goodness Faith meekness Temperance and
the Holy Spirit now says now keep
beholding because by beholding we become
what changed into the same image from
glory to glory why because we are
beholding the
glory the spirit beloved is just trying
to make you look good and so he takes
the work of Christ and he attributes it
to
you but it's not really
yours you didn't really do that
the credit goes to the
spirit but he says I I I want to make
you look
good I want to make you look good so all
I need you to do is just keep focusing
see see now we can begin to understand
in Matthew 11:28 why Jesus said this
watch with me Matthew 11:28 come unto me
Jesus said all you that labor and are
heavy laden and I will give you
rest I will give you rest
Lord what I need to do to be saved I
need you to rest all I need you to do is
strike the pose be still be still and
behold just rest all I need you to do is
behold look at the cross look at the
lamb just behold and when we behold he
says listen you that are heavy laden and
and and in that labor you're going to
stop labor Ing and you're going to stop
being heavy laden you're going to stop
doing your work your own
work and so now what I need you to
understand beloved as we continue to
break this down is that there are two
works that we must be aware of there are
two works that the devil is continually
seeking to get us caught up in work
number one is found in Isaiah 64:6
notice with me the Bible says but we all
are as an unclean thing and all our
righteousnesses are as filthy rags and
we all do Fade as a leaf and our
iniquities like the wind have taken us
away all our works are as filthy rats so
these are all our righteousnesses are as
filthy rats so these this would
represent our own works of righteousness
are yall with me so
far our own work like I'm trying to do
right rightous things what
listen if you're trying to do the
righteous
thing then it's already
corrupt it is already corrupt but there
is another work that the holy spirit is
seeking to save us from so one is the
works of our own righteousness but then
there is another work Galatians chter
5:18 notice with me the Bible says but
if you are
led by the spirit you're not under the
law now watch this now the works of the
flesh are manifest which are these
adultery fornication uncleanness
lasciviousness idolatry witchcraft
hatred variance emulations wrath Strife
seditions heresies uh envying murders
drunkenness rebeling and such alike of
which I told you before as I have said
also in the past that they which do such
things shall not inherit the kingdom of
God so watch this y'all watch
this there is the work of our own
righteousness which is as filthy rags
and then there is the work of the flesh
which is basically
lawlessness there are two works that the
holy spirit is seeking to save us from
thinking that we can do something to
earn salvation so so
holy Works which are really of our own
selves and of Our Own Strength and then
Wicked works the works of the flesh
lawlessness and it's kind of just
mindblowing beloved how how
how it's almost like all Christianity
has fallen into one of these two traps
either they are focused on H H uh uh hey
we're not saved by our own righteous
works and then just say hey the law of
God is done away with we don't need to
worry about Wicked works we just know
that we're not saved by our own works
and so they focus on this set of Works
leaving lawlessness you know and then
for many of us Adventist listen man it's
the law you cannot be Lawless but yet
we're trying to be righteous in our own
strength and do y'all see this put a put
a eight in the chat if you just had a
aha moment put a eight in the chat if
you just had an aha moment there are two
Works beloved and the devil is trying to
get the whole world tripped up on he
doesn't care which one he doesn't care
if you try to attempt your own
righteousness he doesn't care if you're
like oh you know what he you're he
you're just going to do wicked Works he
just wants you tripped
up so the hly the work of the holy
spirit is to save us from both of these
works the works of the flesh which is
wicked nness and lawlessness disregard
for the Ten Commandments and the works
of so-called righteousness hey I deserve
to be saved because look at all that I'm
doing I'm keeping the Commandments you
should save me Lord listen both of those
are error both of those are error come
with me again Titus Chapter 3: 5 this is
why the Bible
says uh um I'm sorry Romans chapter 8
watch this
y'all that the righteous of the law
might be fulfilled in us who walk not
after the flesh but after the spirit so
check this
out God is saying the righteousness of
the law must be fulfilled in us but it
cannot be by our own works by our own
efforts and the righteousness of the law
being fulfilled in US means we're not
doing the works of the flesh do y'all
catch that it's it's this amazing
picture of okay how am I going to get
the righteousness of the law to be
fulfilled in me meaning I'm not
practicing lawlessness but at the same
time I'm not exerting my own energy to
do this I'm not trying to manufacture my
own how was that work and the Holy
Spirit says here's how it works I just
need you to
look I just need you to look you see
this is why Beloved the Bible says in
Hebrews 4 Hebrews chap 4 and verse4 the
Bible says oh I'm sorry I'm sorry Titus
3:5 not by works of righteousness which
we have done but according to his Mercy
he saved us by the washing and of
regeneration and the renewing of the
Holy Ghost which he shed on abundantly
through Jesus Christ Our Savior that
being justified by his grace we should
be made hes according to the hope of
eternal life do y'all see
this not by the works of righteousness
that we have
done our righteousness no no no it is
the by the mercy and the renewing of the
holy spirit so if I'm focused on the
glory of
God the work of the spirit is to renew
me so that I'm no longer practicing the
works of the Flesh and at the same time
I am not
exercising my own righteousness to
accomplish the fulfilling of the law
it's literally happening as a mere
reflex of beholding the Lamb of
God are y'all following this so watch
this and I I see the discussion going
listen y'all I'm I'm I'm I'mma show you
something mindblowing are y'all ready
follow me here follow me this is why
Hebrews chapter 4 Hebrews chapter 4 and
verse4 says
this here's what it says y'all ready
Hebrews chapter 4 verse4 for he spake in
a certain place of the seventh day on
this wise and God did rest the seventh
day from all his Works watch verse 10
watch verse 10 for he that has entered
into his rest that is God's rest has
also ceased from his own works as God
did from his I don't know if you catch
what that is saying you
guys when we enter into the
rest
meaning we are
resting not only from The Works of our
own righteousness but from the works of
the
flesh the way that we get Victory is
simply by resting and allowing the Ghost
Rider to write the victory out for
us so while we're focused on this the
holy spirit is at work yeah you you
notice you haven't done this in like
three weeks huh what haven't done
what wait a minute
what I haven't done that in three
weeks I haven't the thing that I thought
I was addicted to wait a minute it oh
while you were focused on the lamb I was
rewriting your heart I was rewriting
your character I was rewriting your mind
I was rewriting your
book come on y'all come on are y'all
catching this so so watch this watch
this
listen when we behold the cross let me
show you what we are
beholding we are beholding Christ's
righteousness and something happens as
we behold that righteousness because
note with me note with me note with me
uh John chap 3:1 16 let's go to the
screen for God so loved the world that
he gave his only begotten son that
whosoever believeth in him should not
perish but have everlasting life I need
y'all to understand that that that when
you are beholding the cross you are
beholding the fruit of
love you you are beholding the fruit of
love yes Richie the holy spirit is like
let can y'all let me do my
job I'm your Ghost Rider I'm here to
make you look good let give me the
pen you just look and I will take care
of the
rest when we behold the cross we're
beholding love we're when we see the
serpent on the pole when we look at
Christ on the cross we are looking at
the picture of love as I Focus On Christ
the ghost riter
writes as I Focus On Christ the ghost
riter
writes how about this as I look at the
cross beloved I am looking at Joy I am
looking at the picture of Joy why do I
say that Hebrews chap 12:2 looking onto
Jesus the author and finisher of our
faith who for the joy that that was set
before him endured the cross despising
the shame and is sat down at the right
hand of the Throne of God as I'm looking
at the cross I'm not only looking at the
principle of love I'm also looking at
the principle of joy and as I'm
beholding love and joy at the cross the
holy spirit is writing in my mind
love
joy it was for the joy that was set
before him that Christ was on that cross
it was the joy of seeing us redeemed so
as we're contemplating the Cross of
Christ we are seeing literally the
picture of love we are seeing literally
the picture of Joy how about peace we're
talking about the fruit of the spirit
right how about peace notice with me
notice with me Colossians chapter 1:20
and having made peace through the blood
of his cross by him to reconcile all
things unto himself by him I say whether
of things in heaven or things on earth
when we are beholding the cross beloved
we are seeing the picture of Peace
Christ did this to establish our peace
with
God as I'm St as I am beholding the
sacrifice of Christ I am looking at the
principle of love I'm looking at the
image of Joy I'm looking at the image of
Peace what about longsuffering according
to 1 Peter chap 3:18 the Bible says for
Christ also has once suffered for sins
the just for the unjust that he might
bring us to God being put to death in
the flesh but quickened in the spirit
listen y'all you want to know what
longsuffering is longsuffering is
suffering
long beloved listen to me Christ
suffered on the cross on our behalf and
as we are beholding his suffering on the
cross the spirit is writing in US
suffering long long suffering endure
listen listen it is by beholding what
Christ did on the cross that that the
Holy Spirit can begin to write on us the
fruit of the spirit love joy peace
longsuffering what about gentleness
which is the same word for kindness well
according to Ephesians chapter 2 verse4
but God who is rich in his Mercy for his
great love where with he loved us even
when we were dead in sins has he
quickened us together with Christ by
grace are you saved and has raised us up
together and made us sit together in
Heavenly places in Christ Jesus that in
the ages to come he might show the
exceeding Riches of his grace in his
kindness in his
kindness toward us through Christ Jesus
Clint you're asking how long can you
focus on the cross we're going to be
focusing on the cross throughout all
eternity
so God is saying I need you to start
focusing on the cross now it is at the
cross beloved that we get a picture of
the kindness of God what about the
goodness of God we've been talking about
that this whole sermon it is the
goodness of God it is the goodness of
God that as we behold that on the cross
the holy spirit is now writing in our
hearts goodness what about faith
according to Hebrews 12:2 looking on to
Jesus the author and finisher of our
faith who for the joy that was set
before him despised the shame and is sat
down at the right hand of the Throne of
God it was the faith of Jesus that held
him up there on the cross what about
meekness listen beloved as I Focus On
Christ The Ghost Writer writes say it
with me as I Focus On Christ The Ghost
Writer rights and he puts within me the
impulses to do right to live right but
it is not my own impulse it is placed
there by the spirit of
God he says I need you to focus to look
and allow me to work in you yes Christie
meekness is not weakness according to
Philippians 2:5 the Bible says let this
mind be in you which was also in Christ
Jesus who being in the form of God
thought it not robbery to be with God
but made himself of no reputation and
took upon him the form of a servant and
was made in the likeness of men and
being found in fashion as a man he
humbled himself and became obedient unto
death even the death of the Cross do I
catch
this as we look at the cross beloved we
are looking at a picture of love joy
peace longsuffering gentleness goodness
Faith meekness and the last the last
fruit is temperance meaning self-control
I need y'all to understand that it was
self-control that led that that kept
Jesus on the cross Matthew 27:42 he
saved others himself he cannot save if
he be the king of Israel let him now
come down from the cross and we will
believe him do you know how many of us
if that was us we we would have been
like wait what you telling me to come
down off let me show you I can come back
listen that's no self-control
y'all it was Jesus's self-control his
Temperance that kept him on the cross
and
so I need you to understand as we focus
on Christ The Ghost Writer writes the
glory which is of Christ is given to us
as I Focus On Christ the ghost riter
writes as I Focus On Christ The Ghost
Writer writes the spirit magnifies the
glory of God by showing us the cross and
as we behold the cross The Ghost Writer
writes and then gives us the
credit listen not only is the spirit
making us more into the character of
Christ but watch this according to
Galatians 5:16 and we're almost there
guys we are almost done Galatians 5:16
the Bible says this I say then walk in
the spirit and you shall not fulfill the
lust of the flesh now let me pause here
walk in the spirit and you shall not
does that sound familiar to anyone walk
in the spirit and you shall
not where do you hear those those three
words you shall ye shall what does that
sound like where do where do where do
you find a whole bunch of ye shall
not
anyone ye shall
not yes Christie you find the ye shall
not in the Ten Commandments if you walk
in the spirit the ye shall not become
reality if you walk in the spirit the ye
shall not become reality see here's what
I need you to understand John 16:13 the
Bible says how be it when he the spirit
of Truth come he will guide you into all
Truth for he shall not speak of himself
but whatsoever he shall hear that shall
he speak now watch this and he will show
you things to
come he will show you what are things to
come what would you call that we talk
about hey the Bible talks about things
to come what are things to come what's
the word we use for that things to
come
prophecy prophecy this is why this is
why the Bible calls the Holy Spirit the
spirit of Prophecy the holy spirit is
the spirit of Prophecy because the Holy
Spirit shows us things to come now when
we think of Prophecy we typically think
of you know Babylon and midd Persia and
Greece and Rome and and external
prophecies but what about the prophecy
of
you what about your prophecy what about
your
future you you see Beloved the reason
Jesus said in Matthew 5:17 come on
follow this y'all Jesus said in M
Matthew 5:17 do not think that I'm come
to destroy the law of the prophets I did
not come to destroy but to fulfill you
ever heard about fulfilled prophecy hey
was prophecy fulfilled or no was
prophecy fulfilled did it happened did
it come to pass Jesus said don't think
I'm come to destroy the law I'm come to
fulfill it that's a
prophecy why why is he coming to fulfill
the law so that watch this so that the
fulfilling of the law might become a
reality in us the righteousness of the
law Romans chapter 8 will be fulfilled
in us that's a prophecy and how does
that prophecy happen how does your
prophecy take place according to Ezekiel
36:27 let's read it again let's read it
again Romans I'm sorry Ezekiel 3627 and
I will put my spirit within you and
cause you cause you to walk in my
statutes so beloved check it
out when the spirit of God has got our
attention and says don't focus on your
own wounds don't focus on your own
misery don't focus on don't look at the
serpents on the ground I just want but
Lord what am I this over here pay
attention pay attention focus on
justification by faith focus on the
Christ of on the cross of Christ focus
on the good tree that's all I want you
to do as that is happening the spirit
now begins to write watch this watch
this watch this look at the screen
y'all as you're focusing on Christ the
Holy Spirit begins to write yes yes you
keep focusing and you will have no other
gods before me
you keep focusing you keep focusing and
you will not any longer make any graven
images to bow down to you keep focusing
and you keep focusing and you will not
not a commandment you better not it's a
promise you keep focusing and you will
not take the name of the Lord in vain
you keep
focusing and you will be like the
prophecy in Isaiah 56 which talks about
the Gentiles taking hold of the Sabbath
that's a new testament thing y'all also
the sons of the strangers that join
themselves to the Lord to serve him and
to love the name of the Lord to be his
servants everyone that keepeth the
Sabbath from polluting it and taketh
hold of my Covenant even them will I
bring to my Holy Mountain and make them
joyful In My House of Prayer their burnt
offerings and their sacrifices shall be
accepted on my Altar for my house shall
be called the house of prayer for the
prophecy of the Gentiles coming in to
keep the Sabbath will become a reality
in you why because the holy spirit is
saying listen listen here's the promise
I'm fulfilling it in you now I am
writing out my law in you listen the
watch come back to the screen y'all the
promise is yes you keep focusing and you
will honor your father and your mother
you keep focusing and you will no longer
kill you keep focusing and yet you will
no longer commit adultery keep focusing
and yet you will stop steal you will not
steal that's a promise you will not
steal as long as you focus on me you
will not bear false witness against you
as long as you're focused on me you will
not covet your neighbor's house or your
neighbor's wife or your neighbor's man
servant or main servant beloved by
beholding by beholding we become
changed option
one we can do the works of our own
righteousness option two we can can work
the works of the flesh which is
lawlessness option
three we can
rest we can rest by simply focusing on
the cross of Christ and watch as the
spirit removes our own
righteousness teaches us not to depend
on our own righteousness which are
filthy rags and at the same
time edits out our past sins and redeems
us from the works of the
Flesh and as we continue to Behold the
Lamb of God the spirit will even become
our speech
writer Luke 12:12 for the Holy Ghost
shall teach you in the same hour what
you ought to
say
yeah y'all the Holy Spirit becomes your
speech
writer option three all day long Earl
Pastor it can't be that simple just
look imagine the children of Israel in
Wilderness in the wilderness it can't be
that we we've been bitten this is real
Poison you mean just
look just
look sister white you can't be serious
are you saying hanging on the cross
Christ was a go if we can just fix the
eyes of men on the gospel on the cross
that's it we can step aside don't we
have to tell them you got
look
look just
look and I want you to understand
beloved that as we look there is a fire
that will begin to burn in our hearts it
is the fire of the righteousness of
Christ so that now when feeding the
homeless and we're doing this and doing
that and doing that we're not doing it
out of a sense of condemnation okay I
got to do these things to show that I'm
righteous no we're now doing it because
we are simply enamored with a picture of
love joy peace La we're not doing it out
of fear we're doing it out of love we're
not doing it out of if I don't do these
things I'm going to be lost so I better
do these things we're doing it out of a
pure motivation of love for the picture
of the man hanging on the
tree Revelation 14:6 and I saw another
angel fly in the midst of Heaven having
the Everlasting gospel to the
Everlasting gospel to preach unto them
that dwell on the earth to Every Nation
Kindred tongue and people saying with a
loud voice watch this y'all saying with
a loud voice
fear God and give glory to
him how do we give something that we do
not have in order to give glory to God
we must first have that glory to
give and this is why the Bible says in
Matthew 5:14 it says you are the light
of the world a city set on a hill cannot
be hid watch this
neither do men light a candle and put it
under a bushel but on a Candlestick that
it may give light to all that are in the
house let your light so shine before men
that they may see your good works wait
your good
works look at that ghost rider look at
that Ghost
Rider the Ghost Rider said your good
works that they may see your good works
and glorify your father in Heaven look
at that go the Ghost Rider is something
else he is he's just
amazing he's just amazing your good
works you and the Holy Spirit looking at
each other like
yeah your good work you didn't write it
but your good
works let your light where did we get
the light from remember when Moses went
up to the Mount and he was with God God
and he came back down and his face was
lighted up with the glory of
God Beloved the way we get our faces
lighted up with the glory of God Is by
fixing our eyes on Jesus and as we fix
our eyes on Jesus and see that he came
to redeem us not only from The Works of
the law our Sunday keeping friends but
also from The Works of the
flesh lawlessness
a disregard for the Commandments the
balance of the holy spirit says not your
own righteousness and not the works of
not
lawlessness I'm going to I'm going to
teach you what it means I'm going to
write the law in your heart and you will
love to do God's
will you will love to do God's
will
John 17:22 we got one verse after this
John 17:22 the
glory which thou gavest me Jesus says I
have given them that they may be one
even as we are one I need y'all to
understand that Jesus wants us to have
this glory and the message that we are
to take into the world about the glory
of God the message we are to take into
the world about the glory of God listen
to me
it is a
message of the
cross it is the message of the Cross you
see many beloved in the Christian
churches do not really understand the
cross the glory that is to lighten the
Earth at the end of time is a picture of
what Christ did for us and what it means
to redeem us from sin and Beloved the
ghost riter is here he is the one that
ultimately seals us beloved listen to me
let me tell you the end then we're done
end result
y'all as we behold the glory of God the
glory of Christ as we worship him as we
as we understand that Glory The Ghost
Writer writes and credits it to us and
why is The Ghost Writer doing all this
very simple y'all he wants your book to
be published he wants to get you
published y put put put an aid in the
chat for this y'all put a Aid in the
chat the ghost riter wants your work to
be published and to stand the test of
time that means he's trying to get you
published in the book of
life if you write your own book it's not
getting
published if you want to be in the
Lamb's Book of Life you better get a
ghost
writer cuz your work is not going to be
good
enough Revelation 217 our closing text
and there shall in no wise enter into it
anything that defileth neither what
soever worketh Abomination or maketh a
lie but they which are written published
in the Lamb's Book of Life if you want
to be published if you want to get your
book published and you're looking for a
good publisher you're looking for a good
Ghost Writer
and today you're saying Lord forgive
me forgive
me for attempting to establish my own
righteousness for trying to manufacture
and force righteousness instead of
taking that time to look and simply
behold you and trusting that if I
actually behold you if I actually just
look you have promised that I will
live Lord train me teach me what it
means to
gaze to look to
contemplate to meditate to let it be my
bread day and night to think on that
thing so that the ghost
riter can do his
work help me to get out of the
way help me to give him the
pen and as he says Behold the Lamb of
God that takes away the sin of the world
you behold and I will work in you and
through you so that the righteousness of
the law will be fulfilled in you I will
justify you by your faith and be
beholding what I did for you on the
cross it will have real life
ramifications the world will look and
say look at that man's good works look
at that woman's good good works but
they're not your
works it's the work of Jesus
so seven in the chat if you want a ghost
rider you want the Ghost Rider seven in
the chat Lord I need the Ghost
Rider I need the Ghost
Rider to take over my
work so teach me
Lord teach me Lord to labor to enter
into that
rest teach me Lord to labor to keep my
eyes
stayed on the Lamb of God and I will
trust that as I do that you will be
working changes in
me in an imperceptible way I will
trust that you who began a good work in
me will see it
through to the end heavenly
father thank you for
speaking Lord may we strike the
pose may we learn what it means to
look and live may we learn what it means
to
understand that justification by faith
will not have one thread of human
devising in the robe of
righteousness Lord many of us struggle
thinking well there's something that I
must have to do works that
I
yes we the people of God will be found
with good works but the good works are
not our own help us to understand that
the only way to get those works is by
focusing our
Gaze on
Jesus contemplating his amazing
sacrifice at the cross so that the fruit
of the spirit may become a reality in Us
by beholding we may be changed and saved
both from The Works the filthy works of
our own righteousness and the filthy
works of the
flesh thank you Lord for being so
patient with
us heal Us by your stripes is our prayer
in Jesus name amen and
[Music]
amen